airdroid.com 2019-12-18

# AirDroid | Delight Your Multi-Screen Life

## What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site or software, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form.

When ordering or registering on our site or software, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, email address, mailing address, phone number or credit card or debit card information. You may, however, visit our site or software anonymously.

## What information can AirDroid access?

Depending on the Android permissions you have granted to AirDroid, AirDroid may be able to access your personal or sensitive data (including personally identifiable information, financial and payment information, authentication information, phonebook or contact data, microphone and camera sensor data, and sensitive device data), to provide you relevant features, like viewing mobile app notifications, managing photos, view and edit contacts, record phone screen and audio, take photos, etc.. AirDroid doesn't store those information on its server without your explicit consent.

This app uses the Device Administrator permission on Android. It is used for the Find Phone feature. To improve security, the “Password enabled” and “Maximum inactivity time lock” security policies will also be enforced upon the activation of the Device Administrator permission.

## Why AirDroid installs Bonjour?

Some AirDroid features, including Nearby, relies on Bonjour to function normally.

## What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

To improve our website or software  
(we continually strive to improve our website or software offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

To improve customer service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

To process transactions  
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site or software feature

To send periodic emails  
The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

## How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

## Do we use cookies?

Yes, Cookies are small files that a site or software or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site or softwares or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site or software traffic and site or software interaction so that we can offer better site or software experiences and tools in the future.

## Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website or software, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site or software policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

## Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website or software. These third party site or softwares have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked site or softwares. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site or software and welcome any feedback about these site or softwares.

## Your Consent

By using our site or software, you consent to our privacy policy.

## Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

www.airdroid.com
